[{"answer": "my friend?! WHERE IS HE?", "docId": "Jason-X.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Hockey player? He's not a ..", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Hockey player? He's not a ..", "docId": "Jason-X.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Old Earth", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Where is he", "docId": "Jason-X.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No, you're dead! You're all dead", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "That's nine to four, gee", "docId": "Jason-X.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You got lucky. I could have waited until he ate your head", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "We must assume the machete was an intricate part of the game of hockey", "docId": "Jason-X.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Thinking with your dick again, my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "We could convert fission transistors", "docId": "Jason-X.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What are you gonna do, tell me", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "My father's company imports and exports. Archaeology is part of the business. We happen to get along just fine, smartass. Look, why don't you bust somebody else's balls for a change", "docId": "Jason-X.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You thought I meant...too tough to apologize, huh? You must have been a very lonely girl", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " I'm on my way", "docId": "Jason-X.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " I'm coming, I'm coming", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "If we don't sever the hull completely she'll drag us down with her", "docId": "Jason-X.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Blew half his skull away, one leg, one arm and left his entrails stretched across the lab. And look at me! I'm covered in his filthy blood", "docId": "Jason-X.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "A real mamma's boy that one. Dissed his mamma and he nearly threw a tantrum. Little good it did him", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Shut up, my friend", "docId": "Jason-X.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " I know you", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "  Oh great...yeah, having a great time, and you", "docId": "Jason-X.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Old woman", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Ka", "docId": "Jason-X.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " I missed you too", "qsentId": 26}]